<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About on Lotus Docs Example Site</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/docs/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About on Lotus Docs Example Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 19:20:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/docs/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 18:19:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/about/about/</guid>
      <description>This website aims to present a general idea of the content in the website, an insight into the team who developed it, as well as its Accessibility Statement. This website aims to provide comprehensive assistance for individuals and teams creating technical documentation websites utilizing Hugo. This platform has been meticulously crafted to empower users with the knowledge and tools necessary to leverage Hugo effectively in their documentation projects. Additionally, we highlight some of Hugo&amp;rsquo;s most valuable features, enabling users to maximize the potential of this powerful tool in their website development endeavors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explanation</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/about/about-explanation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 18:19:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/about/about-explanation/</guid>
      <description>This page aims to showcase how the About page was made.&#xA;Hugo generates the content of its static websites (mainly) through Markdown files. Most of the features explained on this page serve as a Markdown overview. However, Hugo&amp;rsquo;s additional functionalities will also be highlighted.&#xA;Text linkGeneral text is written normally by writing our content without any tags or labels. For example:&#xA;This website&amp;#39;s objective is to provide comprehensive (...)&#xD;Produces: This website&amp;rsquo;s objective is to provide comprehensive (&amp;hellip;)</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
